works great for my box turtles they are
still young and living inside so this is
a perfect hideout for them been
searching far and wide for an underwater
shelter for my 20 year old adult male
red deer slider this was pretty much the
only thing i could find that was
remotely large enough to accommodate him
for your information he's about three
pounds and his carapace measures about
seven inches from head to tail overall
it's pretty great he just fits if he
wants to get away from his basking lamp
but also enjoys laying on top of it
minus one star for the paint inside
starting to bubble and chip away when
being cleaned not a huge issue and i'm
grateful it's not flaking off underwater
to be accidentally consumed by the
turtle but something that warranted a
mention not sure if the picture does it
justice he's a little over a year old at
least a foot long no sharp edges it's
really hard to find a good rock shelter
for my tortoise but finally i have found
it this is a very well built rock fort
in my picture i have it partially buried
in the heat light den area of one of my
enclosures my tortoise petty has tons of
room to easily make it inside as well as
burrow at it i highly recommend this to
anyone with a smaller species tortoise
also it has held up beautifully with
heat light on it as well as the gentle
misting the tank plants get when they
are planted by it not shown in picture
i'm propagating them today bought as an
alternative to the zoo medha hut as soon
as i put it in the pen my russian went
straight over and burrowed in i really
like how sturdy and wide it is too came
in good protective packaging too in
great time very pleased would highly
recommend to anyone wanting either
something different than the zoo med
haber heart or just a nice home for
their reptile we've had this cave for
about four months now and my beardy
loves it she is fully grown and fits
inside pretty well she also likes
hanging out and sleeping on top of it